[
  {
    "question": "@everyone What has to be broken before you can use it? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Egg",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone I speak without a mouth and hear without ears. What am I? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Echo",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone What gets wetter the more it dries? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Towel",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone The more of me you take, the more you leave behind. What am I? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Footsteps",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone What can travel around the world while staying in the same corner? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Stamp",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone What has one eye but can’t see? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Needle",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone What has hands but can’t clap? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Clock",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone I’m tall when I’m young, and I’m short when I’m old. What am I? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Candle",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone What has a neck but no head? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "Bottle",
    "user_id": null
  },
  {
    "question": "@everyone What comes once in a minute, twice in a moment, but never in a thousand years? ***(Answer will be revealed later this evening)***",
    "answer": "The letter M",
    "user_id": null
  }
]
